Previously on Sleepy Hollow...
前情提要
Jennifer Mills, you've helped your sister before.
Jennifer Mills 你之前帮过你妹妹
Abbie wants me to bring you into this, says you'll be valuable.
Abbie想让我来找你 她说你能帮上大忙
But I need to know...
但我要知道...
- Are you in or out? - In.
- 你干不干? - 干
You fell in love, you get married,
你们相爱 结婚
but the whole time you have no idea that your wife is a witch.
但你从不知道你的妻子是女巫
- Correct. - How could you not know?
- 是的 - 怎么可能不知道啊?
She was protecting me.
她要保护我
We are part of an ancient order sworn to fight the darkness that hides in Sleepy Hollow.
我们身负古老的使命 要与沉睡谷的黑暗势力抗争
We're dealing with forces so beyond our control. Beyond beyond.
我们面对的势力太过强大 太过太过强大
Jenny!
Jenny
That's the key, Lieutenant.
这就是关键 中尉
Now, more than ever, we need Katrina.
我们前所未有地需要Katrina
What is it you're afraid to say? I believe I know why I am here.
- 你不敢说出口的是什么? - 我知道我为何在此
- Why? - Ichabod!
- 为什么? - Ichabod!
I'm pulling up to it right now. Yes, I'll send you pictures.
我在路上呢 好 我一会儿给你发照片
I can't believe it used to belong to my family.
真不敢相信它曾经属于我们家
I know. I'm just so curious.
我知道 我就是特好奇
I want to learn everything I can about this place.
我想知道这个地方的一切
It's one of the oldest homes in the area.
它是这一片最古老的住宅之一
It took me five years to secure the title.
我用了五年才保住这头衔的
Oh I'd like to restore it to its original grandeur.
我要让它重现昔日的光彩
We have a lot of work to do.
要做的可多了
I love it.
爱死它了
Really?
真的?
It's history, Sam. My family's history, to be exact.
这可是历史 Sam 准确地说 我家族的历史
So show some respect.
所以放尊重点哟
Things happened here that need to be remembered. Looks haunted.
- 发生在这里的事情值得铭记 - 像鬼宅
For a bodyguard, you are a very fearful man.
作为保镖 你胆子太小了
Lena. Lena!
Lena Lena
Until we know it's structurally safe in there, you are not go...
我们不知道建筑结构是否安全 你不能...
It's amazing.
超酷炫
We should restore all of this.
应该全都恢复原样
Stubborn little brutes.
这倔玩意
Sam! We should've brought the hedge clippers!
Sam! 咱们应该把修灌木的剪子拿来
The place is completely...
这儿根本就是...
I'm merely noting the eradication of a thrice-daily tradition,
我只是想提出 一日三餐的传统现在已经消失了
wherein each meal is treated with the proper allowance of time.
每餐都不能给予足够的时间来享受
Not that the "drive-through" wasn't impressive.
虽说"驾车外带"的确令人惊叹
And despite this establishment's nomenclature,
而且此餐厅虽然取了这个名字
this resembles no Scottish meal I've ever eaten.
但它和我吃过的苏格兰菜丝毫不同
These are from the Austrian Netherlands, for one thing.
首先 这是奥属尼德兰的东西
And dreadfully prepared.
做得也十分糟糕
This is probably as much of a Thanksgiving as we're getting.
咱们感恩节可能也就这么过了
What about your sister? This is "family time. "
你姐姐呢? 这可是"团圆之时"啊
I don't think my having conservatorship over her since her release from the nuthouse necessarily leads
她从精神病院出来后 我是她的监管人 我们可没法瞬间回到
to "pass the cranberry sauce. "
"帮我拿一下红莓酱呗"的模式
The what?
什么酱?
Turkey, cranberry sauce, pumpkin pie.
火鸡 红莓酱 南瓜派
You know, all the stuff the Pilgrims ate.
清教徒当初吃的那些东西
The Pilgrims didn't have any sugar to make a sauce,
清教徒当初可没有糖用来做果酱
let alone a pie.
更别说派了
And venison, not turkey, was served.
而且吃的是鹿肉 不是火鸡
It would've been a miracle for a single half-starved pheasant...
否则可神了 让一只半饱的野鸡...
Hold up.
停
Pheasants?
野鸡?
All this talk of holidays, turkeys, family time...
人人都在说节日 火鸡 团圆...
irks me.
我很烦恼
Because of Katrina.
因为Katrina
If I can't be with my wife during a time of thanks and celebration,
如果在这感恩和欢庆的时刻 我不能和妻子在一起
why must there be so many constant reminders of the inescapable fact that I...
为什么别人还非要没完没了地提醒我 我不能...
You're alone.
你很孤独
I mean no disrespect.
我无意失礼
Your company holds the greatest value to me.
你的陪伴是我最大的安慰
Crane...
Crane
You have a right to be angry.
你有权利生气
You've lost more than anyone ever should.
你失去的比谁都多
Besides, what are holidays for if not airing our grievances?
而且如果节日里还不能倒倒苦水 那节日还有什么用?
After our nuptials,
婚礼过后
I had such hope for the life Katrina and I were to share.
我对将与Katrina共度的生活充满憧憬
It's been a crazy few weeks.
这几个礼拜太可怕了
You'll feel better after a night off.
歇一晚上 你就会好点
Crane, Mills... Got something for you.
Crane Mills 有东西给你们看
Kindly inform me when that night arrives.
哪天晚上能歇了请告诉我
So much for the proper allowance of time.
咱们享受午餐的时间可能太长了
Lena Gilbert... Philanthropist, author, socialite.
Lena Gilbert 慈善家 作家 社交名流
Miss Gilbert's lineage goes back generations, to the Founding Fathers.
Gilbert小姐的祖先可以追溯到开国元勋时期
She looks great in fancy dresses, too. Why is she our concern?
她穿舞会服也挺好看 怎么了?
That was two days ago. No one has seen her since.
那是两天前的照片 后来没人再看见她
Normally, not a problem, but she didn't show up at a fund raiser in DC last night.
按常理这没什么 但昨晚在华盛顿的集资会她也没去
About an hour ago, the Senate Majority Leader contacted me personally to check on her whereabouts.
一小时前 参议院多数党领袖私下联系我 询问她的行踪
Apparently we're not supposed to lose track of billionaires.
我们可得牢牢掌握亿万富翁们的行踪
Sorry... I'm not mistaken... You did just say she is a...
抱歉...没听错的话...你说她是...
billionaire, correct? Yes.
- 亿万富翁 对吗? - 是
Meaning she has a billion... dollars?
就是说她有一亿...美元?
That's the gross national income of all 13 colonies, in my lifetime.
这可是我一辈子能看见的13个殖民地的总收入
Sounds like a rich lady took a wrong turn on the way to her country home.
大概就是富家女回乡间小屋路上拐错了弯
Any of the other units can handle it.
别的人也能处理啊
A member of her staff faxed this over... Copy of a note they found in Lena's handwriting on her desk.
她的一个下属发来了传真 他们在Lena桌上发现了她留下的字条
That's your wife's name, isn't it?
那是你妻子的名字吧?
I thought you might be interested.
我觉得你可能感兴趣
Okay, yeah, that's an interesting coincidence,
好吧 行 有趣的巧合
but if she's supposed to be in DC, how do we even know that she is still in the area?
但如果她应该去华盛顿 我们怎么知道她现在还在不在?
Her assistant tracked the GPS on her car.
她的助理追踪了车上的GPS
The last ping was here in Sleepy Hollow.
最后的地点是在沉睡谷
After that... fell off the map, disappeared.
之后...不知道 消失了
Keep me posted.
记得跟我汇报
It could be a different Katrina.
可能是别的Katrina啊
It's not just Katrina.
不是单单一个Katrina
"Katrina C.," as in "Katrina Crane. "
"Katrina C."是"Katrina Crane"简写
One initial does not a connection make.
一个首字母也不能说明什么
Oh, you've surely come to realize by now, Lieutenant, that when the two of us are involved,
中尉 你现在总得认识到 只要跟咱俩有关
rarely is a coincidence a coincidence.
巧合就不会只是巧合
The captain said Miss Gilbert's lineage
队长说Gilbert小姐的祖先
dates back to the Founding Fathers.
可以追溯到开国元勋时期
Could your... wondrous Internet
你们...奇妙的互联网
perform a search on Miss Gilbert's ancestry?
能否搜索出Gilbert小姐的先人呢?
What are we looking for?
我们要找什么?
Ties to landowners within the confines of the Sleepy Hollow area.???????????
- 沉睡谷范围内的地主 - 好吧
Dating back to my era.
追溯到我的年代
Gilbert.
Gilbert
All right, father's side,
好了 父亲这边
ownership of New World Steel, Dune Chemicals...
名下有新世界钢厂  Dune化工厂...
mother's side, maiden name... Fredericks.
母亲这边 婚前姓...Fredericks
Owned mining interests, invested in railroads.
入股矿业 投资铁路
Seemed like they owned half the Eastern Seaboard at one time.
他们一手掌握半个东部沿海啊
Of course.
对了
Fredericks Manor.
Fredericks庄园
Named for Lachlan Fredericks,
以Lachlan Fredericks命名的
influential landowner and charter member of the Continental Congress.
有势力的地主 大陆会议的发起人
Needless to say, a keen supporter of the war effort.
无需多说 是战争的热心拥护者
And, I assume, a friend of yours.
我猜 也是你的朋友
I know where Miss Gilbert went.
我知道Gilbert小姐去了哪里
I pulled the land title and deed from city hall.
我从市政厅把地契拿来了
This place has had a few different owners,
这地方易了几次主
but no one's actually lived here for more than a few weeks since Lachlan Fredericks.
但自从Lachlan Fredericks之后 没人住过多于几个星期
It's empty. Inside, maybe?
没人 可能在里面?
It's not possible.
不可能啊
Fredericks Manor... This is where you wanted to go, right?
Fredericks庄园...你说的就是这儿吧?
It is indeed.
确实是
But it hardly resembles the residence Katrina and I visited during the war.
但这与我和Katrina战时来拜访时一点都不一样了
Katrina had been requesting to visit the estate for months.
Katrina要求了好几个月 要来看这处房产
Finally, my schedule allowed me to accept an invitation.
最后 我腾出时间接受了邀请
We had such a beautiful day together.
我们共同度过了美好的一天
Ichabod, we must find our gracious host.
Ichabod 我们一定要去看看亲切的房主
Welcome to Fredericks Manor. May I take your coat? Thank you.
- 欢迎来到Fredericks庄园 我可以为您拿大衣吗? - 谢谢
The manor belonged to Lachlan Fredericks.
这个庄园属于Lachlan Fredericks
I knew of him as a dedicated supporter of the war,
他是战争的衷心拥护者
a close friend of Washington's, but I had no knowledge of his other causes.
华盛顿的密友 但我对他其他的事业并无了解
Look around, my love. What do you see?
看看 亲爱的 你看到了什么?
They're all free. They choose to work here.
他们是自由的 他们自愿在这里工作
This estate is a safe haven.
这里就是安全港
A place for anyone seeking refuge.
让每个人都可以寻求庇护
Is that not beautiful?
多美啊
Everyone there, regardless of the color of their skin,
那儿的每个人 无论肤色
was free and guaranteed Lachlan's protection.
都是自由的 并获得Lachlan的保护
This was a sanctuary.
是个圣地
Most of the manor's visitors were former slaves.
大多来拜访庄园的都曾是奴隶
Many of them remained in Lachlan's employment,
他们很多人就留在Lachlan手下工作
earning a fair wage, as every human should.
像所有人一样 公平赚取薪水
I can't fathom how such beauty fell into such ruin.
我无法理解那样的天堂如何破败至此
Or why somebody who dated George Clooney would want to buy it.
也不懂一个跟乔治克鲁尼约过会的人 为啥要买这儿
An Irishman?
是爱尔兰人?
Miss Gilbert?
Gilbert小姐?
Unbelievable.
难以置信
Sheriff's Department! Let me see your hands!
派出所! 举起手来!
Show me your hands now!
马上举起手来!
Lord...
天呐
His face.
他的脸
Looks like some kind of animal attack.
像是某种动物攻击的
Sam Calvern.
Sam Calvern
Works for a private security company.
在一家私人保安公司工作
I'm gonna assume this guy was with Lena.
我猜他是和Lena一起的
Lieutenant...
中尉
They're fresh.
血是新的
Looks like she was dragged away from here. Miss Gilbert may still be alive.
- 她可能是从这儿被拖走的 - Gilbert小姐也许还活着
Charlie-six-two, requesting additional units.
C62 我需要增援
Six-two, did you copy?
62 听到了吗?
No signal.
没信号
Gonna try outside.
去外面试试
Jammed shut. Allow me.
- 卡死了 - 容我来
There's gotta be another way out of here.
有别的路出去吧
This is not happening. Not to be an alarmist...
- 不是吧 - 我无意危言耸听...
But we're in a damn haunted house.
咱们进了该死的鬼屋里了
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==- 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==- 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://www.ragbear.com==- 断头谷 第一季第9集
-==http://www.ragbear.com==- 断头谷 第一季第9集
-=破烂熊字幕组=- 时间轴：断头狗
-=破烂熊字幕组=- 翻译：黄先生 校对：断头袋 时间轴：断头狗
These boards are stuck fast. There must be an exit.
板子被钉牢了 肯定得有个出口
I am not staying in here.
我不会呆在这儿的
Do you understand what I'm saying to you?
听明白没有?
That is not going to happen. We're trapped in here.
- 不该这样啊 - 咱们被困住了
Likely for a reason.
应该有原因的
I'm uncertain what this house desires from us, or Miss Gilbert.
我不清楚这座房子想从我们 或Gilbert小姐身上得到什么
If she's still alive, I assume our best course of action is to locate her
如果她还活着 咱们最好的做法就是找到她
and ensure her safety. Right. Good plan.
- 保证她的安全 - 对 好计划
Hello?
有人吗?
Lieutenant? Where are you going?
中尉? 你干什么?
- Did you see her? - Who?
- 你看见了吗? - 啊?
The woman.
那个女的
- She was right in front of us. - What woman?
- 她就从咱们眼前过 - 什么女的?
All right.
好吧
We've faced witches,
我们见过女巫
a headless rider of death,
无头死亡骑士
a demon who invades our dreams,
还有侵略梦境的恶魔
I'm sure we can brave this little crisis.
我们一定能勇敢面对这次小危机
I am saying haunted houses do not work for me.
鬼屋可不会吓着我
Not as a child, not now, not ever.
小时候 现在 以后 都不会
There's a line.
还差得远呢
She's not here. Let's move on.
她不在这儿 走吧
Wait...
等等...
Gulliver's Travels.
格列佛游记
Swift.
斯威夫特著
Katrina's favorite novel.
Katrina最喜欢的小说
She owned a copy identical to this.
她那本和这个一模一样
- What is it? - It's a letter.
- 是什么? - 一封信
- It survived all these years. - Addressed to Katrina?
- 竟然经过了这么多年 - 写给Katrina的?
One I wrote to her.
我写给她的
The morning I faced the Horseman.
在我直面骑士的那天早上
"My beloved. "If this missive reaches you,
"我的爱人 若此信到你手上
"it means the worst has come to pass and I have fallen in battle. "
即意味着最坏之事已降临 我已倒在战场"
I had asked Washington's aide-de-camp to deliver it
我嘱咐华盛顿的副官 如果我在与骑士的对抗中死去
should my mission to confront the Horseman prove fatal.
就请帮我送信
Which he would have done, several days later.
几天之后 他应该就送去了
She must have returned here while you were buried.
把你埋起来以后 她一定回过这里
And leave my letter in her favorite book?
把我的信夹在她最喜欢的书里?
It's as though I was meant to find it.
就像我注定要找到它
- I don't understand. - Me neither.
- 我不明白 - 我也是
Something's not right about it.
有哪里不对劲
We gotta find this woman.
我们得找到这个女人
Miss Gilbert?
Gilbert小姐?
Sheriff's Department.
派出所
Lena?
Lena?
So it wasn't like this before,
以前不是这样哈
all haunted and with crows?
闹鬼啊 乌鸦啥的?
No...
不...
At the height of the war, this was a place of hope,
战争白热之时 这是希望之地
a force for good.
是善良的力量
When we finally met our host,
终于见到房主时
he was charming, warm, intelligent...
他英俊 温和 智慧...
everything Washington said he'd be.
就像华盛顿给出的评价一样
Ichabod Crane,
Ichabod Crane
I am your most ardent admirer, sir.
我是你最忠实的崇拜者 先生
May I present our house matron.
我来介绍一下房屋的女总管
Mrs. Grace Dixon, your reputation for helping
Grace Dixon夫人 您对有难之人的帮助
those in need precedes you.
让您声名远扬
In retrospect,
回首往日
it is very possible that their home was also a refuge from supernatural threats.
那里同样也是躲避超自然威胁的避难所
Lachlan and Grace talked of evil. Considering the state of this place,
Lachlan和Grace谈起过邪恶 从此地的状况判断
it stands to reason that some demonic force
显然某种恶魔势力
caught up with them, targeted this place,
缠上了他们 盯上了这里
turned it from a sanctuary to a prison.
将它从圣地变为监牢
If someone or something had it out for Lachlan,
如果有人或东西找上了Lachlan
maybe they've had it out for Lena, too.
那他们也可能找上Lena
She is his descendant. You may well be right.
- 她是他的后人啊 - 你很可能是对的
More evidence of Miss Gilbert's struggle.
更说明Gilbert小姐挣扎了一番
After you. I insist.
- 你先吧 - 不同意
Miss Gilbert?
Gilbert小姐?
The closet.
柜子
Oh, my God. Miss Gilbert, we are here to help you.
上帝啊 Gilbert小姐 我们是来帮你的
It's okay. We've got you.
没事了 有我们在
No, don't do that.
不 别那样
Crane...?
Crane?
Please... You don't understand...
拜托...你们不明白...
This house is alive!
这房子是活的!
We've got you.
没事了
The roots... They dragged me.
那些树根...他们拖住了我
- They wouldn't let me go.
不让我走
I don't know what it was. It's okay. Breathe.
- 我不知道是什么 - 没事了 呼吸
Come and sit, come and sit, come and sit.
坐下 坐下 坐
All right, look at me.
好了 看着我
Hello. Now, it's my understanding
你好 就我所知
that you are a descendant of the man who lived here,
你的祖先是曾经住在这儿的人
Lachlan Fredericks.
Lachlan Fredericks
He was an ally to a great and true cause,
他协助了一项伟大而正义的事业
and as brave a soul as I ever met.
是我所见过的最勇敢的人
So why don't we honor his memory
为表示对他的缅怀
by getting out of this nightmare in one piece?
我们要好好地走出这场噩梦
Mills, where are you?
Mills 你在哪儿?
Just 'cause it's the holidays, doesn't mean you don't have to check in.
虽说在过节 但你也不能不汇报啊
Call me back. Your sister's here. I'm dealing with her B.S.
给我回电话 你姐姐来了 跟我这儿满口胡话
- Someone's in a mood. - Yeah, you have no idea.
- 某人不高兴啊 - 还用你说
You better have what I asked for.
你最好有我要的东西
Thanks for the loaner.
谢谢借我枪那人
- You stole that. - We were fighting demons that were trying to bust out the Horseman.
- 是你偷的 - 我们当时对付的可是要释放骑士的恶魔
There was a lot of confusion. I lost track of what gun belongs to where.
全都搞混了 我记不住哪把枪是哪儿的
I left you that message five days ago.
我五天前给你留的消息
- I'm here now, aren't I? - The rest?
- 我这不是来了吗? - 另一把呢?
Come on, don't waste my time. I thought it was a gift.
- 快点 别浪费时间 - 还以为就送给我了呢
You know, for helping save everyone's ass? Cigars are a gift.
- 我可帮你救了大家的命 - 雪茄可以当礼物
Jewelry is a gift.
珠宝可以当礼物
Maybe I'm a different kind of girl. This conversation is over.
- 大概我是个与众不同的姑娘 - 谈话结束
- So... - As in, you leave.
- 就是... - 就是你该走了
Fine.
好吧
It was a stupid idea anyway.
反正这想法也挺蠢的
What? It's just, it's the holidays...
- 是什么? - 就是 节日了嘛...
- And...? - Nothing. Forget it.
- 所以...? - 没啥 当我没说
I was thinking of having people over for Thanksgiving dinner
我想请大家来吃感恩节晚餐
to say thank you to Abbie for taking me in, and I thought, you know,
感谢Abbie收留了我 你知道 我想
if you didn't have plans... You're gonna cook?
- 如果你没什么事的话... - 你要做饭?
I can cook.
我会做饭
So this is a normal dinner type thing.
就只是正常晚餐啥的
You make turkey and gravy, I bring some pie.
你做火鸡和肉汤 我带点派去
- Crane and Mills will be there? - Yep.
- Crane和Mills也会去? - 对
We act like normal people for a change.
咱要换口味当正常人
One night only, I promise. Then I go back to stealing from you.
就一晚 我保证 然后我就回来继续偷你东西
- That's funny. - Um, am I interrupting?
- 有意思 - 打扰你们了吗?
Macey is here.
Macey来了
- I-I can come back. - No, no, this is Jenny Mills.
- 我可以一会儿再来 - 不用 这是Jenny Mills
And, uh, I was just leaving.
呃 我正要走
Hey, I wasn't expecting you.
嘿 没想到你会来
Aw, my little bean.
我的小宝贝
There's gotta be another way out.
一定有另一条出路
Another exit we haven't thought of yet.
一个我们还没想到的出口
Miss Gilbert, you left a note on your desk.
Gilbert小姐 你在书桌上留了一张字条
You'd circled the name "Katrina C."
圈起了这个名字"Katrina C"
Katrina Crane.
Katrina Crane
I found her name in a registry from the late 1700s.
我在18世纪末的一张登记表上发现了她的名字
She was the last person who came here for sanctuary before the manor was abandoned.
她是庄园废弃前 最后一个来寻求庇护的人
My name is Ichabod Crane. Katrina was my...
我叫Ichabod Crane Katrina是我的...
Relative. He's related to her.
亲戚 他们有亲属关系
Would you mind telling us what you're doing here?
能告诉我们你来这儿干什么吗?
Um, this place has always been a family mystery.
这地方一直都像是个家族秘密
No one knows what happened to it or to my great-great-great- whatever-grandfather Lachlan.
没人知道这房子 或者我的曾曾曾曾祖父Lachlan发生了什么
When I found that registry with Katrina on it,
后来我发现了写着Katrina名字的登记表
I thought maybe I'd found the key to unlocking the truth.
我觉得我找到了解开秘密的钥匙
So I bought the manor back and came here, hoping something would make sense.
于是我买回了庄园 回到这儿 希望能弄清什么
And yet you've found no clue as to what dark force took hold of this refuge?
但你没发现是什么黑暗力量控制了这个避难所?
Just a legend that Lachlan was more than a passionate abolitionist.
只有传说 Lachlan并不仅是积极的废奴主义者
That he was also involved in witchcraft.
他还和巫术有关
That might explain why Katrina was so keen to visit this place.
那大概能解释Katrina为何那么想拜访这里
If your ancestor was a warlock,
如果你的祖先是个术士
using witchcraft to protect those seeking refuge on his property,
用巫术来保护到此寻求庇护的人
perhaps he was a member of my...
那他也许就参加了我...
relative's coven.
亲戚的女巫集会
Did you just say "coven"?
你刚说了"女巫集会"?
Katrina was a witch,
Katrina是个女巫
and a very dear friend of your forefather's.
是你先人亲近的朋友
When I freed you from those roots, they bled.
我帮你解开树根的时候 它们流血了
Whatever malevolent being attacked this house,
不管是什么怪物袭击了这房子
triumphing over Lachlan's protections,
击破了Lachlan的保护
it has infested the property. Something terrible happened here.
- 它就寄生在这里 - 这儿发生了可怕的事
And it had something to do with Katrina.
跟Katrina有关
There must be some answer, something in your research.
一定有某种答案 就在你的研究里
Possibly, but all of it's back in New York.
可能吧 但那些都在纽约
Okay, it's time to go.
行了 该走了
- What is it? - Quickly.
- 是什么? - 快走
Crane, there was something back there.
Crane 刚那里有东西
Something bigger. Yes, I saw.
- 更大的东西 - 对 我看见了
??????????????????????
现在怎么办?
We can't stay back here. Where would you have us go?
- 不能躲在这儿 - 你说去哪儿?
Everyone...
各位...
Go ahead. I'm right behind you.
走 我在你们后边
Lieutenant, come on!
中尉 快!
Crane!
Crane!
Lieutenant! Down here!
中尉! 在下面!
Lieutenant!
中尉!
Stand back.
往后站
Give me your hand. Your hand.
把手给我 手
Lieutenant, give me your hand.
中尉 把手给我
Miss Gilbert...
Gilbert小姐...
Oh, no.
哦 不
Crane? Where are you?
Crane? 你在哪儿?
Crane?
Crane?
It's time.
时候到了
Ex-Excuse me...
不 不好意思...
That was good, Mills.
真行 Mills
Talk to the ghost.
都跟鬼说话了
Excuse me.
不好意思
Coming through.
借过
Thank you.
谢谢
Not gonna say hello?
不打个招呼吗?
I mean... you're dating my dad...
我是说...你在跟我爸约会...
there's no point being a coward about it.
没什么可害怕的
- We have to meet at some point. - I'm not dating your dad.
- 咱们早晚要见面的 - 我没跟你爸约会
I don't even really like your dad.
我都不怎么喜欢你爸
Sometimes me, either.
有时候我也是
Macey.
Macey
Jenny.
Jenny
You're so not a cop. Definitely not.
- 你太不像警察了 - 必须不啊
My sister is. Must be cool.
- 我妹是警察 - 够酷
Having a sister to look out for you like that. Uh, yeah. Can be.
- 有个妹妹罩着你什么的 - 对 可以很酷的
She's a bit of a hard-ass.
她可有点狠呐
Try growing up with my dad.
想想跟我爸长大是啥日子
Honestly, I can't even imagine.
说实话 真想不出
Well, you know, it's better now.
其实 现在好多了
He works here. I live in the city.
他在这儿工作 我住城里
The man's always busy, so, you know, I don't really have to deal
他总在忙 所以 你懂的 我基本不用
with his BS much of the time.
应付他那些废话
Just me and my mom. I'm cool with that.
只有我和我妈 我觉着挺好
I never had much of a mom or dad.
我没怎么和爸妈在一起
Don't know what it's supposed to be like, but...
不知道那该是什么样 不过...
maybe give him a chance.
给他个机会嘛
He's not a completely terrible person.
他也不是完全烂透了
Just some friendly advice.
友情建议而已
I know it's not the most romantic spot, but...
这儿不是最浪漫的地点 但是...
it's private.
很私人
I'll make this brief. I know, um, I know you're busy.
长话短说 我知道你很忙
Just so you know, there is nothing going on between...
你要知道 并没发生什么 我和...
Whatever you do on your own time is-is none of my business.
你私下里做什么我管不着
But how you behave as a parent is.
但你要尽父亲的责任
One weekend... That's all Macey's seen from you since you transferred here.
一个周末...自从你调到这儿 Macey就见了你这么久
One weekend.
一个周末
All she knows is-is "something came up. "
她唯一知道的就是"出了点事儿"
I call every day, Cynthia...
我每天都打电话 Cynthia...
You know what? It's not working.
知道吗 这样不行
When you were assigned here...
你被分到这儿的时候...
it was supposed to be better for everyone.
我们以为大家都能更好
Smaller town, easier...
小镇子 更轻的...
workload, a place where Macey can get out of the city.
工作量 Macey可以出城玩
Your words. I'll make it up to her.
- 都是你说的 - 我会补偿她
All I see is a small-town precinct...
我只看见这么小的一个辖区...
a tenth of the size of your old one.
是你以前那个的十分之一
What could possibly be such a challenge in Sleepy Hollow?
沉睡谷到底能遇到多大的挑战?
Cynthia...
Cynthia...
I know it doesn't make sense, but the work I'm doing here is important.
我知道这样说没用 但我的工作非常重要
Okay. Well, then why can't you have someone else handle it?
好 那你为什么不能派别人干?
I can't.
我不能
- It has to be me. - Do you hear yourself?
- 必须我来 - 听听你的话
Is this the kind of father you want to be?
你就想当这种父亲?
I'm trying, Cynthia.
我在尽力了 Cynthia
I want to make things right with Macey. That's why I moved here.
我想和Macey融洽起来 所以才搬来这儿
What happened, happened.
木已成舟
And we're dealing with it, she's dealing with it, and she's doing well.
我们就得面对 她面对了 而且她做得很好
But it won't last...
但未必能长久...
if you hide from your responsibilities as a father.
因为你在逃避作为父亲的责任
She needs stability...
她需要支持...
not any more disappointment.
而不是继续失望
There's no other way to say this.
我没有别的办法来说
I had some... papers drawn up...
我...拟了几份文件...
demanding full custody.
我要求全部监护权
If you cancel one more weekend... I will file.
如果你再一个周末不回来...我就提交
For her sake.
是为了她
You would do that to me?
你会这么对我?
This is not me.
不取决于我
This is you, Frank.
而是你 Frank
Crane? Lena?
Crane? Lena?
It's coming.
要来了
Hurry.
快
The pain is rising. She's close now.
疼痛在加剧 马上就快了
The child is coming.
孩子要出生了
- Please, are we safe? - You and your child are safe.
- 请问 我们安全吗? - 你和孩子都很安全
All you need to do is bring this life into our world.
你只要把这个生命带到我们的世界
I can't do it.
我做不到
Look at me, Mrs. Crane.
看着我 Crane夫人
I can't do this, - not without Ichabod. - You have to.
- 我做不到 Ichabod不在 - 你必须做
For your sake and the child's, hmm?
为了你 为了孩子 好吗?
Now, breathe.
现在 呼吸
That's it! That's it. You're doing beautifully.
就这样 就这样 你做得很好
Now push. That's it.
使劲 就这样
Push!
使劲!
Good. That's it. A blanket.
好 很好 拿毯子来
The baby's coming. Now...
孩子要出来了 现在...
Strength, now.
准备 快
Push!
使劲!
Good. That's it.
很好 就这样
Mrs. Crane...
Crane夫人...
it's a boy. I have a son.
- 是个男孩 - 我有儿子了
I have a son.
我有儿子了
Lieutenant, shh, shh, shh.
中尉 嘘 嘘
This way. What happened to you?
- 这边走 - 你怎么了?
- Where is Lena? - The creature took her.
- Lena呢? - 那个生物抓走了她
Dragged her away like a toy. I couldn't stop him.
把她像玩具一样拖走了 我制止不了
Obviously, the creature is more than simply an agent - of destruction. - Crane, I need to tell you something.
- 那个生物显然并非仅是为了破坏 - Crane 我要告诉你件事
- He infested this place for a reason. - Crane...
- 他侵占这里是有原因的 - Crane...
Crane...
Crane...
This was an attack, aimed at Lachlan,
这是一次袭击 目标是Lachlan
who I'm not certain is in league with Katrina,
我不知道他是否是Katrina的同盟
- perhaps even a part of her coven... - It was Katrina.
- 或者她集会的一份子... - 是Katrina
I saw Katrina giving birth.
我看到Katrina在分娩
What did you say?
你说什么?
Downstairs.
在楼下
I had a vision.
我看见一个场景
I saw what happened here.
看见这里曾发生过什么
Katrina came back here because she was going to have a baby.
Katrina回到这里 是因为她要生孩子了
No.
不
No, I'm sorry, you must be mistaken.
不 抱歉 你一定弄错了
She would have told me.
那她会告诉我的
Or she needed to keep it secret.
也许她需要保密
If Lachlan was really part of Katrina's coven,
如果Lachlan真是Katrina集会的一员
it would have made sense for her to come here and give birth.
她回到这里生孩子就说得通了
Come on. Hurry, get her inside.
快来 快 带她进去
She would have figured the protective hex he placed
她一定意识到 他房屋周围的
on the property... would keep her
保护咒...会保护她
and your baby safe.
和你们的孩子
What was it?
男孩女孩?
The baby.
那个孩子
It was a son.
是儿子
You had a son.
你有个儿子
Crane, there's more.
Crane 还有别的
Something happened during the birth.
分娩期间发生了一件事
What happened?
是什么?
Ichabod would be... overjoyed, Katrina.
Ichabod一定会...欣喜若狂的 Katrina
Lachlan, what's going on?
Lachlan 怎么了?
They've broken through the protections. Something came after the baby,
- 他们打破了保护 - 有东西冲这孩子来了
beating the hex by growing inside the property.
生长在房屋里 打破魔法
That creature, the evil in this house,
那个生物 这屋子里的恶魔
attacked the moment your child was brought into this world.
在你孩子出生的一刻 发动了袭击
Lachlan did everything he could to protect them.
Lachlan尽己所能保护他们
Lachlan knew this creature had to be sent by Moloch.
Lachlan知道这东西肯定是摩洛神派来的
Take them now. Use my personal carriage. Go.
带他们走 坐我私人马车 快走
Abbie...
Abbie...
What happened to my son?
我的儿子怎么样了?
Please.
求你
I need to know.
我得知道
I don't know.
我不知道
That's all I saw.
我只看见这些
Then he could have survived.
也许他活了下来
They both could have escaped the creature.
也许他们都躲过了那个生物
Crane...
Crane...
Miss Gilbert, are you hurt?
Gilbert小姐 你受伤了吗?
No...
不...
Miss Gilbert!
Gilbert小姐!
- Miss Gilbert! - Can't get a clean shot!
- Gilbert小姐! - 打不准啊!
Go! Go! Run!
走! 走! 快跑!
Where did she go?
她去哪儿了?
I don't know.
不知道
Lieutenant... the roots!
中尉...打树根!
He's felt it!
他感觉到了!
How do we escape?
我们怎么跑?
This way.
这边
Lieutenant!
中尉!
This way! I found a way out.
这边! 我找到出路了
What are you doing? Stay with Miss Gilbert.
- 你要干什么? - 跟Gilbert小姐留在这儿
My business here isn't finished.
我的事还没完
- Crane... - That thing came after my son!
- Crane... - 那东西是冲我儿子来的!
Listen to me... We're gonna make this thing right.
听我说...我们会搞定这些的
- You just have to stay with me! - Keep her safe.
- 你得跟我留下 - 保护她的安全
- Crane! - Heed my words.
- Crane! - 听我的
Do not follow me.
别跟着我
I know who you serve.
我知道你为谁卖命
I know why you came here.
我知道你为什么来这儿
Did you think you could attack those I love without consequence?!
你以为你可以伤害我爱的人 然后一走了之?
Huh? That you could come for my wife?
以为你可以伤害我的妻子?
My child?!
我的孩子?!
Give Moloch my regards.
代我向摩洛神问好
My God.
我的天
I should like to go home now.
现在我想回家
There you are.
你在这儿啊
So, I'm thinking... Jenny's burnt turkey and gluten-free pumpkin pie
我在想...Jenny烧焦的火鸡 和无谷蛋白南瓜派
might be just what you need to lift your spirits.
大概能让你精神抖擞起来
Okay, it's not the greatest sales pitch.
好吧 这些玩意没啥卖点
There will be rum.
但有朗姆酒
It's your favorite.
你的最爱
Barbadian Best Amber.
巴巴多斯朗姆酒
I believe I would not have survived Valley Forge without it.
如果没有它 我挺不过福吉谷的 (独立战争最艰难的时光)
I'm much obliged, Miss Mills.
我很感激 Mills小姐
But in my present state, I fear I would not be pleasant company.
但以我现在的状态 恐怕不是个受欢迎的客人
Look...
听着...
Thanksgiving isn't easy for everyone.
不是每个人的感恩节都特别好过
When I was a kid, I remember...
我小时候 我记得...
walking on the street, passing houses on my block,
走在街上 经过街区上的一座座房子
looking in windows,
透过窗户
seeing people, families,
看见人们 一家人
sitting around tables, laughing, carving turkeys.
围在桌边 欢笑着 切火鸡
I was just so envious.
我很嫉妒
I wanted that more than anything.
那是我最想要的东西
I had it... in England.
我有过...在英国
During my father's holidays from teaching at Oxford,
我父亲放假时从牛津教书回来
I would sit by the hearth,
我会坐在壁炉边
and he'd regale me with glorious tales
他会给我讲述迷人的
of ancient Greece.
古希腊神话
And I really believed I'd follow his footsteps...
我真切相信我会跟随他的步伐...
I'd be a professor in my own right,
凭自己之力 成为一名教授
yet upheld by his pride for me.
而他会为我骄傲
And that one day, I would have a son,
我相信有一天 我会有一个儿子
and I'd share that same comfort that I felt so freely.
我会让他拥有我曾享受的同样幸福
I'm guessing that's what the point of this is?
我猜这就是过节的意义?
The time for reflection.
让你反思
You see what you have now,
你看清拥有的东西
and you embrace what's in front of you.
拥抱将来的一切
Oh, I nearly forgot.
我差点忘了
This arrived for you this afternoon.
下午来的 给你的
More treasures from the Amazon, perhaps.
又是来自亚马逊的宝藏吧
It's from Lena Gilbert.
Lena Gilbert寄的
The records from Fredericks Manor throughout the years.
是Fredericks庄园这些年的纪录
Documentation on Mrs. Grace Dixon...
关于Grace Dixon夫人的文件
the manor's house matron.
她是庄园的女总管
A list of her progeny.
她后裔的名单
Family tree.
家谱
Lori Roberts.
Lori Roberts
My mother.
是我妈妈
You're a descendant of Grace Dixon.
你是Grace Dixon的后人
My ancestor brought your son into this world.
我的祖先接生了你的儿子
Quite heroically.
非常英勇
I see the family resemblance.
我能看出家族相似性
It seems that you and I...
似乎你和我...
our paths were intertwined from the very start.
咱们两个的轨迹从一开始就缠在了一起
It definitely would seem.
可不是嘛
We have a drink.
来喝一杯
It's a day of giving thanks.
这可是感恩的一天
To family. To finding family.
- 敬家人 - 敬找到了家人
破烂熊字幕组 -==http://www.ragbear.com==- 欢迎加入
破烂熊字幕组 -==http://www.ragbear.com==- 欢迎加入